

Piotr Korlaga

java developer









Hello!

I'm a programmer with a three-year track record of building IT solutions for various sectors e.g.: public, energy, telecom, finance. Well-versed in all phases of the software development lifecycle. I strongly believe in Agile, engineering culture and automation what is proven way to bring business value to customers.

Work experience

Full Stack Developer | SMT Software | Remote

06.2015 - ...

Electronic document system and public services for Cracow City Hall

- Backend: Activiti, JPA, JAVA-RX, JAVA-WS, Spring,
 Hibernate, JAXB
- Frontend: AngularJS, SASS, Bootstrap, Orbeon, XML
- Databases: PostgreSQL
- Servers: **Tomcat, Nginx**
- Tests: TestNG, Mockito, Selenium
- Others: IntelliJ IDEA, Git, Git flow, Jenkins, Grunt, Bower,
 Npm

Tutor | Akademia Programistów | Warsaw

01.2015 - 06.2015

Founding the project which the goal was teaching kids programming skills

Full Stack Developer | Syndatis | Warsaw/Remote

02.2014 - 01.2015

Electronic documents procesing and workflow solutions for pharmaceutical industry, finance and human resources management

- Backend: JBPM, Spring, Turbine
- Frontend: Vaadin, jQuery, Velocity, MooTools, CSS
- Databases: Oracle, MS SQL
- Servers: Tomcat
- Tests: JUnit
- Others: Eclipse, CVS, SourceTree, JRebel

Java and SAS Developer | Execon ITS | Warsaw

06.2013 - 02.2014

Credit scoring systems for banking and telecom industry

- Backend: 4GL, SQL, XML, Eclipse Project
- Databases: Oracle, SASOthers: Eclipse, CVS

Electronic documents processing system for energy industry

- Backend: Activiti, Spring, Hibernate
- Frontend: JSP, jQuery
- Databases: Oracle
- Others: **Eclipse**, **SVN**

Education

Engineer's degree | Military University of Warsaw | Computer Science

2011 - 2014

- receiving a rector's scholarship for the best students
- prize in the competition of Bachelor's thesis
- graduated with mark: very good

Student exchange | JAMK University of Applied Sciences | Computer Science

08.2012 - 01.2013

- attending mobile development courses: Android, Windows Phone, Qt (C++)
- web application course: HTML5, Photoshop and Illustrator (basics)

Beyond work

Activities

- leader of a group of volunteers: Akademia Przyszłości (2011-2015)
- Warsaw Java User Group attendee
- conferenceholic e.g.: Confitura, Codepot, SpreadIT, Boiling Frogs, GDG Dev Fest Lviv, GDG Dev Fest Warsaw, InfoShare, CYBERCOMdev, InfoMeet, CareerCon

Hobby

- backpacking
- fast learning and life hacking
- personal finance and investing